What's on TV?
电视上在播什么节目?
"I love Stuart Bonnett" starring Beth Hobart.
"我爱Stuart Bonnett", Beth Hobart主演.
Justine, don't rub it in.
Justine, 不要老提这个嘛.
What is on TV?
到底有什么节目?
Thriller Theater.
惊险片影院.
Something called "The Jersey devil".
片名是《Jersey魔鬼》.
Cool.
妙极了.
Is that about a couple on a date and they park in the woods or something?
是那个讲了一对约会的恋人把车停在树林的故事吗?
Well, according to the story I know, they run out of gas,
Well, 根据我记得的故事, 他们用光了汽油,
and they're really nervous because there's an escaped monster in the woods, too.
他们十分害怕, 因为树林里还有一只在逃的怪兽.
The Jersey devil.
Jersey魔鬼.
Right.
正是.
They hear a noise and the guy gets out to look around and the woman waits in the car like this.
他们听见一阵嘈杂声, 那男的就出去四周查看, 女的在车里等, 像这样.
She hears scratching behind the car, in front of the car, and against the roof.
她听见嚓嚓声, 在车后边, 在车前边, 还有在车顶上.
And she's scared because of the Jersey devil.
她害怕极了, 因为Jersey魔鬼.
Now I remember.
现在我记起来了.
She finally gets out and sees that it was her boyfriend trying to get back into the car.
她最后走了出来, 看见她男朋友正试图返回车内.
But the Jersey devil got him.
但Jersey魔鬼抓住了他.
It's supposed to be true.
据说是真的.
Did you hear the one about the baby-sitter and the phone calls?
你听过那个保姆和骚扰电话的故事吗?
I think so.
我想听过吧.
The creep calls the baby-sitter and calls and calls and won't let her alone,
那个卑鄙的家伙给那个保姆打电话, 一直不停地打, 让她不得安宁,
and she finally has the operator trace the phone lines.
最后她让接线员追踪电话.
And the operator calls and says, "Get out now.
接线员打电话过来说: "快逃出去.
He's calling from a phone inside the house!"
他就在这房子里给你打电话!"
Ahhhgh!
Hello.
喂.